<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>celson</title>
    <link>https://celson.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on celson</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:00:00 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://celson.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://celson.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://celson.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As a Messaging Platform Engineer at Stone Co., I am responsible for designing, developing, and maintaining the messaging infrastructure that supports real-time communication across our systems. This includes architecting scalable and resilient messaging solutions, integrating with diverse communication protocols (such as MQTT, AMQP, or WebSocket), and ensuring seamless interoperability between different applications and services.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I collaborate closely with software developers, system architects, and DevOps teams to implement messaging patterns that optimize performance, reliability, and security. This involves creating robust APIs for message queuing, handling asynchronous communication flows, and implementing message routing and delivery mechanisms that guarantee high availability and fault tolerance.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sobre</title>
      <link>https://celson.github.io/pt/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://celson.github.io/pt/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Como Engenheiro de Plataforma de Mensagens na Stone Co., sou responsável por projetar, desenvolver e manter a infraestrutura de mensagens que suporta comunicação em tempo real em nossos sistemas. Isso inclui arquitetar soluções de mensagens escaláveis e resilientes, integrar com diversos protocolos de comunicação (como MQTT, AMQP ou WebSocket) e garantir interoperabilidade perfeita entre diferentes aplicações e serviços.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Colaboro estreitamente com desenvolvedores de software, arquitetos de sistema e equipes de DevOps para implementar padrões de mensagens que otimizam desempenho, confiabilidade e segurança. Isso envolve criar APIs robustas para filas de mensagens, lidar com fluxos de comunicação assíncronos e implementar mecanismos de roteamento e entrega de mensagens que garantem alta disponibilidade e tolerância a falhas.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
